<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Hawley Farm Holiday Cottages in East Devon</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Hawley Farm Holiday Cottages in East Devon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 12:45:39 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Story</title>
      <link>/our-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-story/</guid>
      <description>Hawley Farm
We arrived at Hawley Farm in 1984 and milked a herd of cows on the small farm, we had fun and games in bad weather when the milk tanker came to collect the milk and the cake lorry tried to deliver. The hill and the oak trees were not helping us getting large lorries in and out when the snow is on the ground, we can tell you some more stories when you arrive for your holiday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if it rains?</title>
      <link>/what-if-it-rains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/what-if-it-rains/</guid>
      <description>Rainy days when on Holiday at Hawley farm.
 Beer Caves have a very interesting tour of about 1hour ten miniutes in these large caves, it is very cold so go dressed up. Seaton Jurassic - a community-led centre that will engage thousands of people with East Devon’s unique geological, coastal and marine heritage A day out looking around the many antique shops in Honiton as this is what makes up a large part of the shops here from old toys to books a lot to see if you are interested this sort of History.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gardens in East Devon</title>
      <link>/out-and-about-gardens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/out-and-about-gardens/</guid>
      <description>Gardens
Burrow Farm gardens are within the foot path walk no. 4 on the Circular walks in and around Dalwood. So a visit not to be missed. 13 Acres of heaven, now in their 50th year.
If you come in a gardening group of 10 or more Mary can arrange a tour, around the different design styles that make up the colour from 1st April to the end of October. Wild flower meadow, Azalea Glade, Terrace, Rose, The Millennium Garden and more to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/april-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/april-2019/</guid>
      <description>April 2019 The blackthorn continues to flower and so the cold weather remains, sunny in the day, but cold at night, with frosts, not much rain, so the spring flowers are still looking grand and lasting longer than normal.
I would say it has been a super spring and every thing has been looking lovely. We are now in the Easter Holidays and lovely to see children who are interested in what goes on in the countryside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walk this way!</title>
      <link>/info/thingstodo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 19:06:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/thingstodo/</guid>
      <description>Walking the many footpaths, that are right from your door when you stay at Hawley Farm self catering holiday cottages near Axminster and Honiton.
There are five walks that have been timed so you can plan your day and they all pass the Tuckers Arms pub in the village of Dalwood where you will be able to have a rest with food and drink if you arrive at lunch time or from six in the evening, or the small village shop where you can buy an ice cream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>/reviews/guestbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 18:27:26 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reviews/guestbook/</guid>
      <description>Reviews If you would like to predict how good your stay at Hawley Farm will be without any perceived marketing bias of this website, then please look at our
 Reviews on Trip Advisor by clicking one of: Cider Press, Wagon House or Stables. Note however that it is beneficial to book direct, through this website. Reviews on Booking.com. Note however that it is beneficial to book direct, through this website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to find us</title>
      <link>/info/findus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 18:18:14 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/findus/</guid>
      <description>Navigation For satellite navigation, our postcode is EX13 7HR, however the postcode will direct you to our neighbour about 300 metres away at Lower Hawley. You may find it useful to use our precise location on Google Maps (see above). Keen cyclists may also find it useful to inspect the nearby cycle routes. Feel free to pan and zoom the map above in order to explore the surrounding area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When and where</title>
      <link>/info/whenandwhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:43:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/whenandwhere/</guid>
      <description>Where Devon is said to be one of the most beautiful counties in the United Kingdom with history, culture and stunning views intertwined. The Jurassic Coast has a great story to tell and the rolling Blackdown Hills are the perfect place to enjoy a picnic in the warm summer months. Whether you enjoy cycling, walking, surfing or just fancy a pint in the local pub, there are plenty of treasures waiting on Hawley Farm&amp;rsquo;s doorstep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Availability and Booking</title>
      <link>/booking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:24:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/booking/</guid>
      <description>Booking Bookings are managed through Devon Farms, a cooperative of farming holiday providers. Please see the booking form below.
The booking form is restricted to start your booking on a Saturday for Cider Press and Wagon House. The Stables however changes on a Friday, so a 3 or 4 night booking is possible in high season. From October to May, we are happy to relax this restriction, therefore if you would prefer a different period, please &amp;ldquo;contact us&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:24:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Us Please contact us if you have any queries. Also, please let us know how you found your stay with us so that we can continually improve our service.
You can telephone us on 01404831250 or 07968155916. Also, you can email us at: info@hawleyfarm.co.uk, or simply fill out the form below:
Loading... </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ciderpress</title>
      <link>/accommodation/ciderpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 12:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accommodation/ciderpress/</guid>
      <description>Overview Living Area  Authentic wood burner TV and DVD player Wireless internet access  Kitchen and Dining area  Fitted cupboards to store food Fridge, double oven and hob Toaster, kettle and microwave Utility space with freezer, sink, washing machine and tumble dryer  Master Bedroom  5ft double bed En suite wet room with shower, toilet and sink Wardrobe, dressing table TV and DVD Player Glass entrance to garden and patio  Second Bedroom  Choose from a 6ft double bed or two 3ft single beds Wardrobe and drawers for storage TV and DVD Player Glass entrance to garden and patio  Third Bedroom  Choose from a 5ft double bed or two 2ft 6in single beds Wardrobe and drawers for storage TV and DVD Player  Outside area  Lawn, patio and garden Barbecue area with table and chairs for six people Parking spaces for two cars with a car park for more if needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/february-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 05:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/february-2019/</guid>
      <description>February 2019 As the snow melted the sheep found their green grass again to eat. Many sheep keep the East Devon fields tidy in the winter when most of the cattle are not to be seen as they winter in the warm sheds on the farm, being fed the silage that had been made in the summer close to the village of Dalwood.
Some ewes on the Devon Farm have already had their lambs and can be seen in the fields with their mothers, you may think it is too cold for them but as long as their mums give them a good helping of milk to fill their bellys, they are fine out in the cold with their mums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stables</title>
      <link>/accommodation/stables/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 12:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accommodation/stables/</guid>
      <description>Overview Lounge (upstairs)  Country view from large window TV and DVD player Wireless internet access Seating for 6 A sofa bed for +2 A family bathroom just off the stairs  Kitchen and Dining area (ground floor)  Country view from large window Large table for dining up to 10 Range cooker Large fridge freezer Microwave, toaster and kettle Dishwasher Seating  Bedroom 1 (ground floor)  6ft super kingsize bed or 3ft twin beds and 3ft single Large room with seating and storage TV and DVD Player Wetroom ensuite  Bedroom 2 (upstairs)  6ft super kingsize bed or 3ft twin beds Large room with seating and storage TV and DVD Player Shower ensuite  Utility  Sink, washing machine and tumble dryer  Outside  Garden with table and seating for 6 Outdoor balcony area off lounge BBQ and parking  &amp;ldquo;We stayed at the Stables in November, it is well thought out conversion, finished to a high standard, it has everything you could possible need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wagon House</title>
      <link>/accommodation/wagonhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 12:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accommodation/wagonhouse/</guid>
      <description>Overview Living Area  Authentic wood burner TV and DVD player Wireless internet access Separate downstairs WC  Kitchen and Dining area  Fitted cupboards to store food Fridge freezer, oven and hob Microwave, toaster and kettle Utility area with washing machine and tumble dryer Oak tables with four settings  Master Bedroom  6ft double bed En suite bathroom with sink and toilet Wardrobe and desk TV and DVD Player Glass entrance to garden and patio  Second Bedroom  En suite bathroom with double shower Choose from a 5ft double bed or two 2ft6in single beds Wardrobe TV and DVD Player  Outside area  Lawn, patio and garden Barbecue area with table and chairs for six people Gravel and paved garden areas Garden furniture and sun loungers Parking space  &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve just returned from a fantastic stay in the Wagon House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/july/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/july/</guid>
      <description>July 2019 July has gone on record as the hottest month so far; the sun shone and the rain stayed away, even when thunder and lightning were nearby.
So the fields have become brown and dry, with very little grass growth only in the shade is there any green grass. The cows are given a large run of a few fields and have some silage feed on the ground. Half of the herd have been dried up, so are not milking, they are on their rest period before they calve at the end of August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/june/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/june/</guid>
      <description>June 2019 Although the rain came and came, we were pleased to see the much-needed rain as it had been very dry. However, like all good things, it went on a little too long, and we soon hoped for sun, to get to the second cut silage! In the last week, the good weather returned and the silage was cut the second time. The crop was so much better due to the rain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>