<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Hawley Farm</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Hawley Farm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 12:45:39 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Caravaning and camping</title>
      <link>/info/camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 19:06:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/camping/</guid>
      <description>A highly recommended site in the beautiful Axe Valley is Abbey Gate Farm. Please have a look at their website and reviews, you will not be disappointed: www.abbeygatefarm.co.uk
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>/reviews/guestbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 18:27:26 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reviews/guestbook/</guid>
      <description>Reviews If you would like to predict how good your stay at Hawley Farm will be without any perceived marketing bias of this website, then please look at our
 Reviews on Trip Advisor by clicking one of: Cider Press or Wagon House. Note however that it is beneficial to book direct, through this website. Reviews on Booking.com. Note however that it is beneficial to book direct, through this website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When and where</title>
      <link>/info/whenandwhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:43:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/whenandwhere/</guid>
      <description>Where Devon is said to be one of the most beautiful counties in the United Kingdom with history, culture and stunning views intertwined. The Jurassic Coast has a great story to tell and the rolling Blackdown Hills are the perfect place to enjoy a picnic in the warm summer months. Whether you enjoy cycling, walking, surfing or just fancy a pint in the local pub, there are plenty of treasures waiting on Hawley Farm&amp;rsquo;s doorstep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Availability and Booking</title>
      <link>/booking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:24:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/booking/</guid>
      <description>Booking Bookings are managed through Devon Farms, a cooperative of farming holiday lets. Please see the booking form below.
The booking form is restricted to start your booking on a Saturday, however for certain weeks of the year, we can relax this restriction, therefore if you would prefer a different period, please &amp;ldquo;contact us&amp;rdquo;.
We can take payment by cheque, bank transfer and Paypal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:24:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Us Please contact us if you have any queries. Also, please let us know how you found your stay with us so that we can continually improve our service.
You can telephone us on 01404831250 or 07968155916. Also, you can email us at: info@hawleyfarm.co.uk, or simply fill out the form below:
Loading... </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ciderpress</title>
      <link>/accommodation/ciderpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 12:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accommodation/ciderpress/</guid>
      <description>Overview Living Area  Authentic wood burner TV and DVD player Wireless internet access
  Kitchen and Dining area  Fitted cupboards to store food Fridge, double oven and hob Toaster, kettle and microwave Utility space with freezer, sink, washing machine and tumble dryer
  Master Bedroom  5ft double bed En suite wet room with shower, toilet and sink Wardrobe, dressing table TV and DVD Player Glass entrance to garden and patio</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 12:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog1/</guid>
      <description>February 2019 As the snow melted the sheep found their green grass again to eat. Many sheep keep the fields tidy in the winter when most of the cattle are not to be seen as they winter in the warm sheds, being fed the silage that had been made in the summer.
Some ewes have already had their lambs and can be seen in the fields with their mothers, you may think it is too cold for them but as long as their mums give them a good helping of milk to fill their bellys, they are fine out in the cold with their mums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wagon House</title>
      <link>/accommodation/wagonhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 12:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accommodation/wagonhouse/</guid>
      <description>Overview Living Area  Authentic wood burner TV and DVD player Wireless internet access Separate downstairs WC
  Kitchen and Dining area  Fitted cupboards to store food Fridge freezer, oven and hob Microwave, toaster and kettle Utility area with washing machine and tumble dryer Oak tables with four settings
  Master Bedroom  6ft double bed En suite bathroom with sink and toilet Wardrobe and desk TV and DVD Player Glass entrance to garden and patio</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>