<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Infos on Hawley Farm</title>
    <link>/info/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Infos on Hawley Farm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 19:06:49 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in East Devon for the Family</title>
      <link>/info/camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 19:06:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/camping/</guid>
      <description>Walking the many footpaths, that are right from your door when you stay at Hawley farm.
There are five walks that have been timed so you can plan your day and they all pass the Tuckers Arms pub in the village of Dalwood where you will be able to have a rest with food and drink if you arrive at lunch time or from six in the evening, or the small village shop where you can buy an icecream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to find us</title>
      <link>/info/findus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 18:18:14 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/findus/</guid>
      <description>Navigation For satellite navigation, our postcode is EX13 7HR, however the postcode will direct you to our neighbour about 300 metres away at Lower Hawley. You may find it useful to use our precise location on Google Maps (see above). Keen cyclists may also find it useful to inspect the nearby cycle routes. Feel free to pan and zoom the map above in order to explore the surrounding area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When and where</title>
      <link>/info/whenandwhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:43:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/whenandwhere/</guid>
      <description>Where Devon is said to be one of the most beautiful counties in the United Kingdom with history, culture and stunning views intertwined. The Jurassic Coast has a great story to tell and the rolling Blackdown Hills are the perfect place to enjoy a picnic in the warm summer months. Whether you enjoy cycling, walking, surfing or just fancy a pint in the local pub, there are plenty of treasures waiting on Hawley Farm&amp;rsquo;s doorstep.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>