<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Hawley Farm Holiday Cottages in East Devon</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Hawley Farm Holiday Cottages in East Devon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/april-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/april-2019/</guid>
      <description>April 2019 The blackthorn continues to flower and so the cold weather remains, sunny in the day, but cold at night, with frosts, not much rain, so the spring flowers are still looking great and lasting longer than normal.
I would say it has been a super spring and every thing has been looking lovely. We are now in the Easter Holidays and lovely to see children who are interested in what goes on in the countryside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/march-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/march-2019/</guid>
      <description>March 2019 March for us arrived like a lamb with light showers after the dry warm February, sometimes it was like summer
The guests leaving after their half term holiday have had a great time enjoying the beautiful weather and we think this is a lovely time to come away on holiday for many reasons.
The Daffodils are all out, Primroses and the Hawthorn in the hedges.
Finding fossils at Lyme regis and Charmouth can be easy this time of year as with the winter weather there is more uncovered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/february-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 12:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/february-2019/</guid>
      <description>February 2019 As the snow melted the sheep found their green grass again to eat. Many sheep keep the fields tidy in the winter when most of the cattle are not to be seen as they winter in the warm sheds, being fed the silage that had been made in the summer.
Some ewes have already had their lambs and can be seen in the fields with their mothers, you may think it is too cold for them but as long as their mums give them a good helping of milk to fill their bellys, they are fine out in the cold with their mums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/may/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/may/</guid>
      <description>The leaves are out and the trees look great, bright and shiny It is a lovely time of year, the bluebells are everywhere with many others flowers, wild garlic, little violets. The weather has been very dry and a little cold, however a lot of sunshine.
After checking the sheep this evening at 9.30 pm they are still busy eating, blaring and not at all sleepy, the lambs are running around.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>