<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Hawley Farm Holiday Cottages in East Devon</title>
    <link>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Hawley Farm Holiday Cottages in East Devon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/april-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/april-2019/</guid>
      <description>April 2019 The blackthorn continues to flower and so the cold weather remains, sunny in the day, but cold at night, with frosts, not much rain, so the spring flowers are still looking grand and lasting longer than normal.
I would say it has been a super spring and every thing has been looking lovely. We are now in the Easter Holidays and lovely to see children who are interested in what goes on in the countryside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/march-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/march-2019/</guid>
      <description>March 2019 March for us arrived like a lamb with light showers after the dry warm February, sometimes it was like summer. Holiday cottages in Dalwood close to Axminster.
The guests leaving after their half term holiday have had a great time enjoying the beautiful weather and we think this is a lovely time to come away on holiday for many reasons.
The Daffodils are all out, Primroses and the Hawthorn in the hedges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/february-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 05:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/february-2019/</guid>
      <description>February 2019 As the snow melted the sheep found their green grass again to eat. Many sheep keep the East Devon fields tidy in the winter when most of the cattle are not to be seen as they winter in the warm sheds on the farm, being fed the silage that had been made in the summer close to the village of Dalwood.
Some ewes on the Devon Farm have already had their lambs and can be seen in the fields with their mothers, you may think it is too cold for them but as long as their mums give them a good helping of milk to fill their bellys, they are fine out in the cold with their mums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aug-Oct 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/aug-sept-oct-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/aug-sept-oct-2019/</guid>
      <description>August - October 2019 Honiton Show had a lovely day on the 1st August, the run of good weather continued.
Beach days a many with the choice of beaches such as Lyme Regis, Seaton, Beer, Branscombe and Sidmouth close to Hawley Farm, for swimming and taking the sun. Dalwood fair also brought in the crowds, making a splendid day out for all the family when on holiday whilst staying on our farm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/july/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/july/</guid>
      <description>July 2019 July has gone on record as the hottest month so far; the sun shone and the rain stayed away, even when thunder and lightning were nearby.
So the fields have become brown and dry, with very little grass growth only in the shade is there any green grass. The cows are given a large run of a few fields and have some silage feed on the ground. Half of the herd have been dried up, so are not milking, they are on their rest period before they calve at the end of August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/june/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/june/</guid>
      <description>June 2019 Although the rain came and came, we were pleased to see the much-needed rain as it had been very dry. However, like all good things, it went on a little too long, and we soon hoped for sun, to get to the second cut silage! In the last week, the good weather returned and the silage was cut the second time. The crop was so much better due to the rain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/may/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hawleyfarm.co.uk/blog/may/</guid>
      <description>May 2019 The leaves are out and the trees look glorious, bright and shiny It is a lovely time of year, the bluebells are everywhere with many others flowers, wild garlic, little violets. The weather has been very dry and a little cold, however a lot of sunshine.
After checking the sheep this evening at 9.30 pm they are still busy eating, blaring and not at all sleepy, the lambs are running around.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>