<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Hawley Farm Holiday Cottages in East Devon</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Hawley Farm Holiday Cottages in East Devon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/april-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/april-2019/</guid>
      <description>April 2019 The blackthorn continues to flower and so the cold weather remains, sunny in the day, but cold at night, with frosts, not much rain, so the spring flowers are still looking grand and lasting longer than normal.
I would say it has been a super spring and every thing has been looking lovely. We are now in the Easter Holidays and lovely to see children who are interested in what goes on in the countryside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/july/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/july/</guid>
      <description>July 2019 July has gone on record as the hottest month so far; the sun shone and the rain stayed away, even when thunder and lightning were nearby.
So the fields have become brown and dry, with very little grass growth only in the shade is there any green grass. The cows are given a large run of a few fields and have some silage feed on the ground. Half of the herd have been dried up, so are not milking, they are on their rest period before they calve at the end of August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/june/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/june/</guid>
      <description>June 2019 Although the rain came and came, we were pleased to see the much-needed rain as it had been very dry. However, like all good things, it went on a little too long, and we soon hoped for sun, to get to the second cut silage! In the last week, the good weather returned and the silage was cut the second time. The crop was so much better due to the rain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>